<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>erewhon</title>
    <link>https://erewhon.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on erewhon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://erewhon.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentations</title>
      <link>https://erewhon.github.io/page/presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erewhon.github.io/page/presentations/</guid>
      <description>Various presentations I have given, or places I&amp;rsquo;ve spoken. No, nothing earth shattering. But since I present using HTML, might as well dump them here for posterity.
 Bendwood @ Bendwood Elementary (2016-12-12). A friend of my wife&amp;rsquo;s asked if I could talk to her son&amp;rsquo;s computer class. And oh boy did I! (Functional) Reaxtive Web Development @ Houston Functional Meetup (2014-11-19). Clojure @ Clojure Houston Meetup (2013-11-21)? Hadoop for DevOps, including OpenTSDB, Flume, and Scribe @ Houston Hadoop and Spark meetup (2013-04-03) Immutant @ Clojure Houston Meetup (2013-01-24) Cascalog @ Clojure Houston Meetup (2012-12-13)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remaking an online journal</title>
      <link>https://erewhon.github.io/post/2017-10-28-shuffling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erewhon.github.io/post/2017-10-28-shuffling/</guid>
      <description>I have had various online presences for the better part of 20 years. I keep a daily journal, but very few things end up online. I am going to try to write more. Both prose and code. And with time I will probably backfill my other attempts at writing.
Today, I have an old blog at erewhon.flatland.org. I have my business / consulting site at flatland.biz. And who knows what else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://erewhon.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erewhon.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>On this page, I attempt to explain who I am.
My name is Steven Byrnes. See my contacts page if you want to contact me.
Happy? No? Then continue reading dear reader. (Or continue indexing dear Googlebot.)
I have been programming, and working with computers, since the earth cooled. Or at least it seems that way. It’s funny; I usually don’t feel like an old timer. I know a lot of people who have been at it longer than I have, but when I think about it, I started programming (as a kid) almost 30 years ago, I’ve been using Unix &amp;amp; Emacs for close to 25 years, and I’ve been using the Internet for 20 years… Well, that makes me feel like an old timer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>